And while the invocation by our pastor first comes to church, it's really all the pieces.
Father, it's neat to look around this room and see so many people that give and give.
And you know that, and I pray that you will bless each of them just tomorrow, and every day they give.
Father, the ones in front of us as they make decisions tonight give them super wisdom.
And let them distance what you want them to do.
Father, I pray that you will help us continue to trust you for our community.
And for it to please you, but we'd like the employees to thank you for that.
Bless our meeting tonight. Jesus, name my pray.
Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands, one nation, under God, indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.
Four, but again but unskilled in personal praises.
Five, cleanse list.
Motion.
Thank you.
Okay.
Three, four, five, six.
ima.
I don't know.
Okay.
Four, five, six.
Please.
Okay.
All right.
That's it.
Please.
Okay.
Thank you.
Doing the same thing.
Okay.
Thank you.
May I come in?
Okay.
Hi, Parker. Hi. Hey, update and discussion on the community fiber project there.
Next week to talk about the design itself, we went that was not a special deal about what that design was like, how we could put on the phone, that kind of things.
Definitely talking about next. We have, we shouldn't be complete with the design of the bugger HUD, the outside plans and networks engineering, all that should be completed hopefully in November.
So, we went this forward and we should know about the event and hopefully we'll receive a bit and forward a bit first in the first quarter of the year after that we should.
Second quarter we should hopefully start seeing some materials, the timeline, the big time on this stuff is, it can be long.
So, we need a potential we can get there and get the things that's that ordered and that's on the timeline long and they're saying a big push right now for all this fiber projects.
So, that will be important to assume we can get that material to free even if we get some of that stuff ordered together.
So, the other thing is we may have some competition encounters with people that have put in some plans to do some plans.
So, just so you know that I just want to be aware that there's a possibility that we'll have that.
Any questions that I may be able to answer or not answer about where we are in that process?
So, again, actually I'm amendment to work order 19 so that's 20-5 with old and engineering for waterline utility relocation located in industrial park on the state highway 69A between eight tribes trail and Buffalo run road or billboard not to exceed $44,843.
So, tonight we're asking you actually to take no action on this item. There's some other stuff we bring to you along with on this project.
Okay, another new business of any of which has risen since closing this agenda.
We'll have to trust the community announcements.
12 trust managers communication.
Nothing.
13 adrenaline.
5 seconds.